<articles>
	<article>
	
		<title>Difference Between Analog and Digital?</title>
		<text>
		<![CDATA[
			Analog and Digital
<br />As a technology, analog is the process of taking an audio or video signal (the human voice) and translating it into electronic pulses. Digital on the other hand is breaking the signal into a binary format where the audio or video data is represented by a series of "1"s and "0"s. Simple enough when it's the deviceanalog or digital phone, fax, modem, or likewisethat does all the converting for you. 
<br />
<br />Digital versus analog can refer to method of input, data storage and transfer, the internal working of an instrument, and the kind of display. The word comes from the same source as the word digit and digitus.
<br />The digital technology breaks your voice (or television) signal into binary code a series of 1s and 0s transfers it to the other end where another device (phone, modem or TV) takes all the numbers and reassembles them into the original signal. The beauty of digital is that it knows what it should be when it reaches the end of the transmission. That way, it can correct any errors that may have occurred in the data transfer. What does all that mean to you? Clarity. In most cases, you'll get distortion-free conversations and clearer TV pictures. The nature of digital technology allows it to cram lots of those 1s and 0s together into the same space an analog signal uses. Like your button-rich phone at work or your 200-plus digital cable service, that means more features can be crammed into the digital signal. Digital offers better clarity, but analog gives you richer quality. Digital like the VCR or the CD is coming down in cost and coming out in everything from cell phones to satellite dishes. 
<br />
<br />Phone lines 
<br />
<br />Digital lines are found in large, corporate phone systems. Though digital lines carry lower voltages than analog lines, they still pose a threat to your analog equipment.
<br />
<br />Analog lines also referred to as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), support standard phones, fax machines, and modems. These are the lines typically found in your home or small office
<br />
<br />There are digital-to-analog adapters that not only let you use analog equipment in a digital environment, but also safeguard against frying the internal circuitry of your phone, fax, modem, or laptop.
<br />
<br />Cordless phone
<br />
<br />The very nature of digital technologybreaking a signal into binary code and recreating it on the receiving endgives you clear, distortion-free cordless calls. 
<br />
<br />Cordless phones with digital technology are also able to encrypt all those 1s and 0s during transmission so your conversation is safe from eavesdroppers. Plus, more power can be applied to digital signals and thus, you'll enjoy longer range on your cordless phone conversations.
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />The advantage to analog cordless products? Well, they're a bit cheaper. And the sound quality is richer. So unless you need digital security, why not save a few bucks and go with an analog phone? After all, in home or small office environments where you may be the only cordless user, you won't have any interference issues. 
<br />
<br />Keep in mind, when talking about digital and analog cordless phones, you're talking about the signals being transferred between the handset and its base. The phones themselves are still analog devices that can only be used on analog lines. Also, the range of your cordless phoneanalog or digitalwill always depend on the environment. 
<br />
<br />Cellular Phones
<br />
<br />Perhaps the most effective use of the digital versus analog technology is in the booming cellular market. With new phone activations increasing exponentially, the limits of analog are quickly being realized. 
<br />
<br />Digital cellular lets significantly more people use their phones within a single coverage area. More data can be sent and received simultaneously by each phone user. Plus, transmissions are more resistant to static and signal fading. And with the all-in-one phones out nowphone, pager, voice mail, internet accessdigital phones offer more features than their analog predecessors.
<br />
<br />Analog's sound quality is still superioras some users with dual-transmission phones will manually switch to analog for better sound when they're not concerned with a crowded coverage areabut digital is quickly becoming the norm in the cellular market. 
<br />
<br />Better Sound Quality
<br />Digital offers a better quality of sound. Proponents of digital claimed too that because digital scrambled up the signals into bursts, it was more secure than analog and can help thwart "cloning," an act of grabbing phone account information over the air in order to copy then resell that information for piracy purposes. By some industry estimates, close to $650 million in wireless services has been coveted by these big-eared crooks, which only adds onto the operator's bottom line a cost that is eventually passed on to the customer. Digital has stronger battery life than analog, and for the most part, better, more modern features on the phones.
		]]>
		</text>
		<date>01-01-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Types of Generators</title>
		<text>
		<![CDATA[
		Generators are used for the generation of electricity and they ensure that most of the essential appliances can be run whenever there is a power outage. Generators of different wattage capacities can be used according to the needs of the individual. The choice of buying the right type of generator depends upon a number of factors like the wattage capacity, voltage ratings, fuel type, fuel efficiency, noise level, portability and price – a prudent choice can only be made if you knew what to look for.
<br />
<br />Stand By – Standby generators provide backup power in homes and offices and are permanently installed outside the house or office building. They are plugged into the electric circuits or home wiring. – The unit turns itself on and off automatically. They can automatically detect disruption in the usual electric supply and begin supplying power within a few seconds. – Propane and natural gas offer a safe, long-term fuel supply and are more environment friendly than gasoline or diesel fuels. – Like any motor, a generator motor creates quite a bit of heat and needs a cooling system to prevent overheating. Standby generators can be either air-cooled or liquid-cooled. The major difference is that air-cooled systems are louder and not quite as effective. Liquid cooled systems are quieter and more dependable – and also more expensive to purchase and to maintain.
<br />
<br />
<br />Portable – Portable generators are usually used in places where there is no power supply such as construction sites, camps, etc. These generators are sufficient to run appliances like televisions, refrigerators, sump pumps and furnaces. – Portable systems are wheeled units that require to roll the generator outside, start it up, and hook it up to a power inlet box Portable generators supply electricity to selected appliances through extension cords. – They are fueled by gasoline, which can be difficult to store and transport during a blackout. Carbon monoxide is always a concern in the safe use of portable generators. – They are designed to be used for short periods of time only a few hours at a stretch. As a result, they tend to be much smaller and less expensive.
<br />
<br />A related aspect of generator motors is the speed at which they run, as measured in RPMs. Generators made for the US market operate at one of two speeds: 1800 RPM or 3600 RPM. 1800 RPM motors will last longer and run quieter; 3600 RPM motors are smaller and lighter
		]]>
		</text>
		<date>01-02-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Free to Air Receiver and Files</title>
		<text><![CDATA[In today's world, each day brings new inventions and advancements and it would be impossible to keep up with it all. But, with times constantly changing, we have to do our best to keep up with them. One of the latest trends that everyone should know more about is FTAs, free to air satellite receivers and files.
<br />An FTA receiver is a satellite receiver, which is well equipped to receive the unencrypted FTA satellite transmissions. An FTA satellite receiver is able to decode the MPEG-2 data compression protocol used in most of the FTA satellite transmissions. An FTA receiver will not be able to decode the Dish Network or DirecTV satellite signaling.
<br />
<br />SOME OF THE TOP FTA RECEIVERS AVAILABLE IN THE MARKET:
<br />Like: Cool sat 8000 HD, SonicView 8000HD, and Viewsat HD 8000.
<br />Coolsat 8000 HD will allow you to capture and get all of the free-to-air channels in HD. Coolsat 8000 HD also uses brand new updated standards that provide the clearest picture for all HD and non HD TVs. Coolsat 8000HD uses the 200mhz STI CPU that allows it to have quick channel change fast on screen channel guide display and a brand new box design. Coolsat 8000HD is also backed with a full 2 year warranty that covers all parts and labor.
<br />SonicView 8000 HD is a brand new free to air satellite receiver by SonicView. This free-to-air satellite receiver can capture about 20 satellites and 700 channels. SonicView 8000HD has a very sharp NIM video tuner that provides HD 1080I picture. SonicView 8000HD is designed for advanced users who like to spend lots of time on their free to air receivers.
<br />The Viewsat HD 8000 free to air satellite receiver that has been specially designed to connect to HD satellites and pick up over the air HD channels for no service fee or cost, all in high definition. Viewsat HD will be coming out shortly but as of now no official specs are out.
<br />Receiver Files Support: Many companies do provide you with all the free to air BIN Files, latest keys, Free to air Receiver loaders, instructions, video-tutorials, and technical free to air File Support. The support provided the manufactures of Free to air receivers would teach you step by step how to use your free to air Receiver. Right from pointing your Free-To-Satellite Dish to programming free to air Receiver the support will always be provided by the manufacturers and dealers alike.]]></text>
		<date>01-03-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Key Instructions to keep your Children Safe with a Personal Safety App</title>
		<text><![CDATA[As a guardian when children are with us or around us, we give careful consideration to their safety. On the other hand, when we can't see them and they are a long way from us, it gets to be trying to guarantee their safety particularly in a situation where we hear thievery, attack and badgering cases occurring in grounds on an ordinary premise. Concerning children, a personal safety application is exceptionally prescribed to guarantee their safety when they take off to school. Here are a few stages that they can remember, to be arranged against specific threats. 
<br />
<br />
<br />Keep your mobile phone with all of you time and spare essential numbers into your telephone, for example, contact no. of police headquarters nearest to your college grounds, if conceivable you can make an outing to the police headquarters, acclimate yourself, and know how to contact them in the event that there is a crisis. Other imperative numbers to have are no. of close-by healing centers and taxi administrations.
<br />Secondly, keep your personal data safe in a locker as opposed to conveying it with you once a day, for example, standardized savings card, identification, conception authentication or other imperative docs. On the off chance that you are new to the grounds, convey a guide alongside you until you know your environment well. Keep your possessions available be it your portable workstation, knapsack, iPod, wallet, never keep it unattended as these things can make you easy objective for outsiders.
<br />While travelling, abstain from voyaging alone particularly amid late hours, it is constantly better to have your companions with you. Abstain from taking easy routes particularly crossing through back roads, brambles or bushes, these spots are more wrongdoing helpless, stay in sufficiently bright ranges.
<br />Lastly, when travelling or visiting some place at late evening, keep your relatives and dear companions educated about your area, you could keep them informed by sending messages and alarms to loved ones with your GPS area.
<br />Aside from the aforementioned rules, download a personal safety application like OnGuardHelp that can spare you if there should arise an occurrence of a threat or emergency. Application has been intended to furnish clients with continuous hand holding amid the season of risk and misery. Application has 24x7 accessible client emotionally supportive network and continuous GPS area following. At whatever point you discover yourself casualty of any of such happenings, you simply need to tap the application to make a prompt call or send a text to your friends or family.]]></text>
		<date>01-04-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Protect Remote Location And Valuables With Cellular Temperature Monitoring</title>
		<text><![CDATA[Remote temperature monitoring is a smart and safe way of avoiding damage risks to your goods. Using web-based monitors help to reduce the compliance risk that is usual for the safety of valuable resources. There are wide varieties of monitoring solutions meant for the different applications of different industries will help you in number of ways. If you are able to avoid the temperature damages you can assure that your goods stay in top quality conditions, whether they are at home or while you are moving them from point of origin to their point of destination. To use these sensors is easy and simple task so you can install them anywhere for the safety purpose. Using these sensors is being profitable for the large to small sized industries and they have built successful presence for domestic areas as well. Here are the few benefits that you can have with purchasing the remote temperature monitoring systems:-
<br />
<br />Save Cost
<br />Using temperature alarm is really profitable for the safety of your valuables and they must help you to keep the right temperature in the environment. When you have a automated device installed then you will be able to protect your valuables and resources from spoilage that results saving cost. If your refrigeration equipment is sub par and not working properly, you can lose thousands of dollars in spoiled products destroy future transactions with clients and gain a bad name for your company. When shipping goods that have a sensitive expiration date, there is little room for error.
<br />
<br />24/7 Technical Support
<br />
<br />The most effective benefit of these temperature monitors is that you will have 24/7 technical support on the remote location. When vaccine monitoring goes on consistently then you have no need to worry for the patient safety. TempGenius provides a wireless and automated solution with 24/7 monitoring designed for multiple applications with an aim of safety and protection.
<br />
<br />Peace of Mind
<br />One of the greatest benefits that come with using cellular temperature monitoring is that it brings complete peace of mind to the business. You can have constant vigilance of the temperature conditions of a room. All temp log is available in real time so that you can easily access a particular condition at a point which minimizes errors. These devices are completely helpful to save time, money and resources which optimize the peace of mind.
<br />
<br />In this way, using wireless sensors is really beneficial for the large to small sized businesses. If you are ready to take advantage of these wireless temperature monitors then simply prefer to TempGenius for highest quality cellular temperature monitors.]]></text>
		<date>01-05-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Big Data Analytics: Optimizing business environment and performance</title>
		<text><![CDATA[The old adage that "change is the only constant "was never so relevant as in these times when the world has become a global village and how businesses run, sustain and excel depends largely on their ability to stay aware of the latest research & developments in the field of data handling and how fast they adapt to and apply these innovations to their day to day operations. 
<br /> Big data analytics is changing the dynamics of doing business at lightning pace, especially for companies and organizations dealing with large volumes of data, be it net streaming, logs from web servers, social media platforms or other conventional communications mediums like cell phone service providers. Reality TV involving viewer involvement in the form of constant feedback and active participation of the viewers. Surveys, quiz and gaming shows of global scale, international sports and other events involving massive data handling are potential verticals that could make use of the Big Data Analytics. 
<br /> It's a quantum leap from Business Intelligence application to analyze data; the challenges and roadblocks BI encounters can be dealt with by Big Data analytics that can circumscribe and penetrate the hurdles earlier faced. Technologies such as Java programming that support processing of large data that's computed in distributed quarters. This helps in uninterrupted flow or transfer of data at high speeds, and chances of system crashing are minimal. 
<br /> In layman terms, what all this advanced technology does is that it facilitates in depth study of how data behaves (interacts) and this leads to gaining crucial information that eventually helps using this information in increasing efficiency and performance of systems by creating and providing optimal processing. Scattered random data is streamlined and structured to identify newer patterns leading to near accurate prediction in data behavior. The final objective of course is to help industries optimize performance, minimize pilferages, reduce costs and speed up deliverables.
<br />
<br />
<br /> Attributes & benefits of Big Data can be simplified as:
<br /> 1. Using data sets by trying and analyzing them in different permutations and combinations, deriving new unique integration potential through combinations  
<br /> 2. Upscale industry processes at lowest possible costs and room for future adaptation to potential developmental challenges in anticipation through data analysis.
<br /> 3. To provide simplified long term sustainable solutions by use of high volume data. The solutions arrived at can potentially be replicated in similar different business environments, aimed at developing the capability & expertise for offering the valuable information advantage gained as third party consultation to other aspiring and upcoming businesses.
<br /> 4. The data analysis enabled advantage can be used as a contingency readiness tool     
<br /> 
<br />There are technologies that will help you to cut down on efforts needed to extract, consolidate and generate reports. With the help of big data consulting firms can also use predictive analytics to forecast customer and market dynamics.
<br />Thanks to Big Data analytics, organizations can have far more accurate projections into the future course of action and can take pre-emptive measures to divert possible mishaps, and more importantly restructure their strategies in detailed and precise manner. Better, secure and profit augmenting decisions are ultimately reached.  ]]></text>
		<date>01-06-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Why Now Is the Right Time for a Security System</title>
		<text><![CDATA[If your home is not currently protected by a home security system, then it is high time you considered purchasing one. Sites can give you a lot more information about what a good system can do for you and your family. Now is the time to look into this upgrade on your home because crime rates are rising, violent crimes are happening more often, technology is being well-utilized in these systems, and it can help you be better aware of what is happening in and around your home.
<br />
<br />Crime Rates Are Rising
<br />Crimes all across the board have been on the rise for some time now. Different experts from a range of fields have a lot of theories about why this is, but in the end it doesn't really matter. What does matter is that you are made aware of the rising risk to your home and family. Blame the economy, international affairs, racially charged altercations, or anything else you want, but in the end, you need to work now to take protective steps.
<br />
<br />Violent Crimes Are More Common
<br />Crime rates have been rising, as has been stated, but the most troubling trend in all this is that violent crimes in particular are rising faster than any other niche of crime. It is becoming nigh impossible to turn on the news without hearing about someone causing violent deaths and injuries somewhere in the country. These crimes are also happening more and more in residential areas. One of the best ways for you to keep a violent criminal from hurting your family is to invest in a good security system. Sites like www.signalserviceinc.com say that just having a system can keep criminals from coming on your property once they see the signs or equipment. 
<br />
<br />Technology Has Created Incredible Systems
<br />In the past, home security systems were something of a joke and were easily disabled and avoided. As technology has taken some amazing leaps forward, the security industry has followed suit. The incredible technological upgrades that have been made are more sophisticated than ever before. This means that when you invest in a good system, you will be purchasing some of the most recent installations of technological genius.
<br />
<br />You Need to Know What Is Happening
<br />
<br />Something you may not realize is that security cameras at your home are not just to catch criminals, but also to keep an eye on what is happening at your house. This kind of surveillance can be used in many ways including but not limited to the following:
<br />
<br />Knowing when your kids get home from school
<br />Monitoring when teens come home from late nights out
<br />Seeing who is at the door
<br />Watching when a package arrives
<br />Catching street views of the goings on in the neighborhood
<br />Keeping an eye on animals at the house
<br />Knowing your home is safe while on vacation
<br />Seeing which doors have been open and left unlocked
<br />Controlling the lights and temps in the home from remote locations
<br />Communicating with people in your home from remote locations
<br />There truly is great value in knowing what is happening on your property at any given time, and a good security system can do just that for you. 
<br />
<br />These are just some of the main reasons so many people are now investing in home security systems. When it comes to your family, you need to know that you are doing everything you can to protect them. Investing in a home security system can do a lot to prevent harm and damage to your home and your family should the unthinkable happen. Sites like www.signalserviceinc.com can offer even more information about what options are available and how to choose the right system for you.]]></text>
		<date>01-07-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>The Portable Beam Projector: Convenience and Quality Combined</title>
		<text><![CDATA[For most people, the term 'projector' perhaps gives an impression of a really heavy and noisy device that would only be able to display magnified images with distorted output while heating up the entire room in the process. However, high quality modern LED portable beam projectors have redefined the rules of the game in the world of projection drastically. Powerful LED projectors that can easily fit in a small bag now are able to display pictures of such high quality output that they could rival the quality of some of the best DLP projectors of 2005.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Multi-functionality projectors
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />In an age where customers wish to get more value from their purchase, multi-functionality projectors that are able to do more than just beam dull light rays on the screen should certainly be a welcome news. Portable projectors of today are not just built to beam lights, but are able to play sounds through their in-built speaker and even function as DVD players and satellite TV receivers.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Truly portable projectors powered by battery
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />The projectors of the past often consumed a lot of energy and it would be impossible to run it without a suitable power source. But modern portable beam projectors are amazingly efficient that can even be powered by a small battery for 1-2 hours. The highly efficient use of power in the projectors has ensured that they can perform a range of functions at very low energy costs.
<br />
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Compatible with several modern technologies
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />The necessity to carry several external devices with the projector for ensure its compatibility with modern technologies have been eliminated with the modern portable versions. Portable beam projectors like the Android OS powered DVB-S2 can take inputs from almost any device imaginable, ranging from smartphones to most modern satellite TVs on its own. This could not just eliminate unnecessary hassles, but could also save a tremendous amount of money for customers. It's certainly a welcome development for any projection aficionados.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Affordability
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Gone are the days when you needed to shelve out an amount in excess of $500 for getting the very basic quality projectors, just because they were the products of some big brands.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Ideal for both personal and professional use
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />From being used as a storytelling device for your kids to being used in displaying live sports to hundreds of customers in a bar, the current and potential uses of the modern portable beam projector are immense. It can be used across a diverse range of settings, ranging from a meeting room to an outdoor campsite. The portable beam projector has already started to take a significant chunk of market share and its all set to grow further in the near future, with more advances in battery and display technology. So, if you are planning on buying a new projector, choosing a multiple-functionality portable beam projector could indeed be the right decision.]]></text>
		<date>01-08-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Segways and iPhones, World's Greatest Inventions</title>
		<text><![CDATA[Segways can be considered as one of the best inventions in the world at all time. With its usage as transportation, it makes life easier. It can also be used in sports such as polo, golf, racing, or in leisure such as in road trips or sightseeing. It also adds fun compared to the conventional modes of transportation. By using segways, you do not have to use gasoline in order to make it run. This is why this kind of scooter-like transporter is used by many people which is especially popular to the teens. However, people also make use of segways not only for entertainment purposes, but also for work as well. Some pizza delivery services make use of segways to make their deliveries. It's a fun and at the same time less strenuous way of getting transportation.

There are also segways which are hands free which are built for those who are skilled to balance. In case you want to buy one affordable segway can be found through online stores and also local stores as well. You can choose from the different kinds and types of segways that fits your budget and at the same time, one where you can practice your skills. Affordable segway is usually had to find because it is relatively expensive therefore you really have to look for one that is both stylish and good for your balancing skills as well. Check also the mechanics in these segways for you to know the important details such as its maximum capacity, speed, and such.

Aside from segways, smartphones can also be considered as one of the smartest inventions worldwide. Through smartphones people are able to communicate with other people and also, do tasks that before many gadgets are needed but now with just one phone, you can do all tasks simultaneously. This advancement in cellular phones came in the 2000s where people had more knowledge about the technology. Until now, people still want to buy smartphones rather than regular phones found in the market. This is because of its usage and capability to do the tasks which make owners' life easier.

Although smartphones are the best, it is not unknown to anybody that it is much expensive compared to other regular phones. Since these kinds of phones, such as iPhones are expensive, when people buy it they make sure that it is protected and handled with care. To help protect it, there are glass screen protectors available to buy. To know what are the most effective protectors, iPhone 6 plus tempered glass screen protector reviews are making waves in the social media for you to see.

You should only be careful to buy glass protectors that are fake because some of these do not really use the finest materials used to make sure that your iPhone screens are protected with the best protectors that can be made. These iPhone 6 plus tempered glass screen protector reviews are really helpful because it can be used to sort out people's experiences with buying their iPhone gadgets or screen protectors if you think that it is worth the money or not. By reading these you can know what could be the best protector for you and know what might be more affordable to you.]]></text>
		<date>01-09-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Choosing the Best Antivirus in 2015</title>
		<text><![CDATA[If you want to have a computer that is virus-free and running smoothly, you will need to handle difficult situations, such as computer viruses, malware, spyware and Trojan horses with tact. This does seem hard, but that's because it is. But, the good news is that it is possible, and even you can do it. So, the following are some of the ways in which you can keep your computer running like a well oiled machine.
<br />
<br />Testing Labs
<br />
<br />Needless to say, the easiest way of knowing whether an antivirus is really up to scratch is if the name of a particular brand ends up in the newest computer technology list of the labs. That alone is a vote of confidence as to which antivirus will make a difference when it comes to protecting your computer. The name showing up on one of the testing labs list is a clear indicator that the lab considered the particular product worthy enough to be named on its list. Apart from that, having a good test score once on the list is also another plus point.
<br />
<br />But with all the labs out there, which are the ones that matter? You can use the detailed reports from labs such as, AV-Test Institute, Virus Bulletin, Dennis Technology Labs, and so on. These labs test antivirus software by recreating real world scenarios, so you can rest assured that the antivirus software will work once it is installed on your system.
<br />
<br />Hands-On Testing
<br />
<br />Getting your hands dirty if you know what you're doing is also another way of knowing whether an antivirus is up to the mark when it comes to protection. This is a good way of getting a feel of how the product works. Depending on how the antivirus is able to prevent malware attacks, you will get a better idea as to how powerful the software really is. To test an antivirus, you can use one of the many malware hosting URLs and note the percentage that the software was able to successfully block.
<br />
<br />Multi-Layered Protection
<br />
<br />According to the latest computer technologies blogs, all anti viruses distinguish themselves by going the extra mile when it comes to protecting computers. This means that their protection capabilities go way beyond the basic virus scanning or the real time protection. There are even some antivirus software that can rate the URLs that you visit on the basis of how safe they are. Other antivirus software can also block certain processes on the system from connecting to phishing URL's or malware hosting URLs.
<br />
<br />
<br />It is important to note that even the best antivirus software have flaws too, and those flaws can affect the security of your computer, which is the reason why smart users always keep their operating system up to date with the latest software patches. The trick is to find a fix for a problem as soon as it arises. There are certain vulnerability scans that can verify if all the necessary patches are present on a system or if any are needed.
<br />
<br />Behavior-Based Detection & White listing
<br />
<br />There's also behavior-based detection that can protect a computer against malware threats. Although it isn't unheard of for behavior-based detection systems to flag the actions of legitimate programs as well. White listing is another way to solve the problem of unknown programs. Whitelist-based security programs only allow good programs that it's familiar with to run. While using this approach is not always the best option for different situations, it is a useful one nonetheless.
<br />
<br />Features such as, spam filters, Firewall protection, secure browser for carrying out financial transactions, history wiping, secure deletion of sensitive files and credit monitoring along with a feature called virtual keyboard to foil attempts of keyloggers, are all offered by some of the big names in antivirus software such as Kaspersky Anti-Virus (2015), Webroot Secure Anywhere Antivirus (2015), or Bitdefender Antivirus Plus 2015 and so on.
<br />
<br />Ending Note
<br />
<br />While it would be nice if we had the technology that could sniff out a virus like an X-Ray machine at the airport, and pull it out the butt of a program, the sad truth is that it is physically impossible to protect a computer from every virus attack. But, using the aforementioned tips should get you off to a good start in keeping your computer safe from uninvited malware.]]></text>
		<date>01-10-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Increase Productivity And Save Costs With Poultry-farming Lamp</title>
		<text><![CDATA[Poultry industries spend a significant amount of money on electricity bills every year. The lamps built with older technologies could easily and rightfully be blamed for the enormous bills a poultry establishment is forced to pay for power. Although, it would be unthinkable for any poultry farmer to avoid using lamps altogether, reducing excessive costs of using and maintaining them is certainly imaginable today. A simple modification in the lighting can increase the productivity of the farms, as well as reduce costs simultaneously. Such a miraculous solution is imaginable today in the form of LED poultry-farming lamp.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Reduce your power bills
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Energy bills, generally comprises of 7%-15% of the total overheads for any poultry venture. Several reliable industry researches have proven that LED Poultry-farming Lamps can save at least 20% of the total energy cost compared to CFL or incandescent bulbs. Although LED poultry-farming lamps may cost a bit more during the initial purchase, the consequent saving in electricity bills as well as rebates mean that they save more money for the industry within the first year compared to other bulbs. Such lamps also have a longer average operating lifespan of 4000+ hours, requiring nominal maintenance and saving money on replacements.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Increase in productivity
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Even today, lights that are only compatible with the human eye have been used by the poultry industry. However, scientists have determined that the eyes of the fowl are more sensitive towards certain wavelengths and light colors compared to the average human eye. Chickens have been observed to be more productive and less stressful towards lamps that mimic the wavelengths from natural sunlight and moonlight on which they also base their biological cycles. Modern LED poultry-farming lamps are built to mimic natural wavelengths, which thus could reduce the average duration of reproductive cycles for chickens and increase the overall productivity of a poultry farm.
<br />
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Modern lamps compatible with existing settings
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />In general poultry farmers prefer using dimmers for their lamps so that they can control the lighting environment according to their preferences. Modern LED poultry-farming lamps are easily compatible with most dimmers and don't require extensive changes to the system for installation. Innoven, a renowned lamp manufacturer from Korea, alone produces more than 15 variants of poultry-farming lights that can easily fit with any wiring and switch system. Unlike other lamps, modern LED poultry-farming lamps are also compatible with roof-installed solar panels, allowing owners the opportunity to save enormous power costs.
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />Get the best lighting for your poultry establishment
<br />
<br /> 
<br />
<br />LED lamps are among the latest developments in the world of lighting. In particular, LED poultry-farming lamps have been, keeping in mind the best interests of poultry establishments. Over years of testing, many poultry farmers have benefitted from the new development. Thus, get the best from you poultry establishment by using the best lighting in the market.]]></text>
		<date>01-11-2015</date>
	</article>
	<article>
		<title>Choosing the Right Headphones</title>
		<text><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Headphones
<br />
<br /> Throw away those cheaply made headphones that were boxed in with your MP3 player- the right headphones won't be in there, guaranteed. You can actually experience music on a whole different level with investing in a pair of good headphones.
<br />
<br />Headphones or earbuds?
<br />
<br />First of all you need to decide if you want earbuds or headphones. Earbuds are more worthwhile for people who don't have much space to store them. Headphones are bulkier and more expensive but you do have the option of getting wireless headphones, which are perfect for jogging.
<br />
<br />DJ-style headphones are even bulkier! However they offer excellent sound containment. A lot of music enthusiasts get them because they don't skimp on quality and offer less pressure on the eardrum, resulting in a much longer listening time and minimal damage to your eardrums.
<br />
<br />Sound isolation
<br />
<br />Once you've picked the type you want, evaluate the sound isolation. This refers to how much you actually hear while outside noises are blocked. Getting headphones with good sound isolation will waste less battery life as you don't need to increase the volume to hear what you're playing.
<br />
<br />
<br />Earbuds and in-ear headphones are generally better at sound isolation when compared to regular headphones. This is due to the sound-proofing seal they provide when inserted in your ear. DJ-style headphones, too, create a nicely sealed environment around your ear.
<br />
<br />Noise cancellation
<br />
<br />Although noise-cancelling headphones block out background noise, they actually sacrifice audio quality as well. Surprisingly, headphones with noise-cancellation do not sound as good as other headphones in noisier environments.
<br />
<br />Frequency range
<br />
<br />The frequency range is another aspect not to be missed when buying headphones. A wider frequency range results in better sound quality. Anything between the range 10 Hz to 25,000 Hz is recommended.
<br />
<br />Try before you buy
<br />
<br />Test them out before you buy them! The best way to make sure you end up with headphones worth your money is to test them out first. You could try on your friends' pair or go to a store that sells headphones and speakers with samples available for testing. If you're looking for a more convenient option, just order headphones from a reputed online store, like wow.lk, through Cash on Delivery and utilize their 14 day return policy if you're not happy.
<br />
<br />When shopping for headphones, be it regular headphones or fancy bluetooth headphones, just remember that you get what you pay for.]]></text>
		<date>01-12-2015</date>
	</article>
	
	
	
	</articles>